(Bernadette:)This one is of a woman
giving birth in a river.
(Howard:)Okay, that is
the least Jewish thing
(Howard:)I've ever seen in my life.
(Howard:)You feel like Raj is getting
a little carried away
(Howard:)with all the baby stuff?
(Bernadette:)I don't think so.
(Bernadette:)He just wants to be
part of the experience.
(Howard:)All right, if you say so.
(Howard:)What's in the box?
(Bernadette:)Oh, it's an ultrasonic
microphone
(Bernadette:)so we can hear
the baby's heartbeat.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Howard:)That's cool.
(Howard:)Can we try it?
(Bernadette:)Actually, Raj ordered it.
(Bernadette:)He made me promise
to wait till he was here.
(Howard:)So he can be...
(Howard:)part of the experience?
(Bernadette:)Yeah.
(Howard:)I'm surprised he let us conceive
without him.
(Bernadette:)It's a sore spot...
don't bring it up.
(Penny:)It's so cute
and rustic up here.
(Sheldon:)I know.
(Leonard:)Did you see they still have
a video rental place?
(Leonard:)it's like Colonial Williamsburg.
(Sheldon:)Well...
(Sheldon:)cell service is down
to one bar,